Indiana University Folklore Institute Material Culture papers, 1953-1984, bulk 1960-1981 C614
Indiana University Archives
- Student Papers (Box 1)
  - M/C 77/2 Linnemeier, Philip. "The Armstrong Family" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391, Dr. Warren Roberts, December 4, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 77/3 Dotson, Jason C. "An Interview with Mr. Claude Martindale." (North America, U.S., Indiana), F721, Dr. Roberts, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 77/4 Phillips, Christina S., "Stone Head: The Life of Henry Cross-Early Indiana Stone Carver" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F721, Dr. Roberts, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 77/5 Hellenberg, Antony Thomas. "Private Outdoor Shrines" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F721, Dr. Warren Roberts, April 29, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 77/6 Childs, Barry. "Notes on the Work of Keith Craddock, Bloomington Luthier" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F721, Instructor Unknown, December 15, 1975 (Box 5)
  - M/C 77/7 Maddalone, Rosellen. "Research Paper" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391, Roberts, 1974 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/8 Stahly, Ted. "The Sheer House: A Folk House Type" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F720, Dr. Roberts, 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/9 Katzen, Martin. "A Study of a Horizontal Timber I-House in Morgan County, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F720, Dr. Roberts, December 15, 1973 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/10 Gabbard, Samuel R. "A Study of Early Nineteenth Century Houses in Richmond, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391, Dr. Roberts, August 7, 1974 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/11 Kash, Graham S., "John Maxwell, Maker of Dulcimers" (North America, U.S., Tennessee), F721, Dr. Roberts, May 3, 1974 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/12 Seward, Adrienne L. "The Second Baptist Church of Lafayette"(North America, U.S, Indiana), F720, Dr. Warren Roberts, December 1974 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/13 Stewart, Susan. "The Monkey Doll" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F101, El Shamy, Nick Burlakoff (T.A.), 1976 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/14 Platz, Karen A. "Hebron House, Bethel, Missouri" (North America, U.S., Missouri), F720, Dr. Roberts, Date Unknown (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/15 Hayes, Randall E. "The 'Witch House': An Example of a Log Cabin in America with Drafting Prints"(North America, U.S., Indiana), F404, Dr. Warren Roberts, December 5, 1975 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/16 Hammersley, Sheila. "History of a Log House in Vernon, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391. Jens Lund, December 14, 1976 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/17 Kroll, Pamela. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391, Dr. Roberts, Date Unknown (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/18 Tadros, Fawzi. "Khan Al-Khalili and the Wooden Ivory Carvings" (Africa, Egypt), F721, Dr. Warren Roberts (?)., 1975 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/20 Kiesling, Mark, "Barns of Eastern Greene County, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Instructor Unknown, November 15, 1976 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/21 Fernwalt, Debbie. "Quilting" (North American, Southern Indiana), F101, Coelho, November 30, 1972 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/22 Preissner, Leslie. "Fishersfield, New Hampshire" (North America, U.S., New Hampshire), F220, Instructor Unknown, February 26, 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/23 Holliday, Sherry. "Nellie Richardson and her Folklife Traditions" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), F220, December 1, 1976 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/24 Milliner, Mitch. "Cake Decorating" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Elkhart County), F220, Steven Becker, January 4, 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/25 Wallis, Tamara. "Privies: A Study in Folk Architecture" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), F720/721, Dr. Warren Roberts, May 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/26 Brock, Debbie. "Quilting: An Art of the Past" (North America, Indiana, Bartholomew), F220, Steve Becker, December 1, 1976 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/27 Deible, Jo. "Weathervanes." (North America, U.S., Indiana, Bartholomew County, Columbus), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, May 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/28 Smith, Donna A. "Quilting in America" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Marion County), F220, Steve Becker, December 8, 1976 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/29 Miller, Bruce R. "The Nashville House" (North America, Indiana, Brown County), F220, Steve Becker, April 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/30 Dale, Jackie D. "Gone But Not Forgotten Historical & Biographical Descriptions of Tombstones Found in Morgan Township, Owen County, Indiana" (North America, Indiana, Owen County), F220, Dennis E. Coelho, April 24, 1975 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/31 Ridlen, Susanne S. "A Study of Barns" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Cass County), F720, Dr. Henry Glassie, August 1969 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/32 Hill, Dan. "Chair Caning (Seat Weaving)" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Jennings County), F220, Steve Becker, 1976 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/33 Leach, Celinda. "Graveyard Art in Monroe County" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, 1976 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/34 Ladyga, Nancy. "Barns" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Lawrence County), F220, Steven Becker, December 8, 1976 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/35 Coleman, Juliana. "Folk Art-Quilts" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), F384, Instructor Unknown, 1969 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/36 Perkins, Ken and John Jenkins. "The Canada Homestead" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F101, John Vlach, June 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/37 Pell, Bob. "Don Bagard – An Indiana Wagonmaker" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Clay County), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown(?)., 1976 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/38 Moran, Hertha H. "Advent Calendars of the Henning Sorenson Children" (North America, U.S., Indiana, DeKalb County), F220, Instructor Unknown, December 6, 1973 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/39 Altman, Cathy. "The Traditional Ways of Quiltmaking" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), F391, Dr. Roberts, April 21, 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/40 Bennett, Sandi. "An Early Account of Quilting" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F391, Dr. Roberts, April 21, 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/41 Arterburn, Cindy. "Quilts" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Bartholomew County), F220, Betsy Adler, June 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/42 Mellman, Nancy. "Traditional Rug Weaving" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), F220, Adler, 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/43 Hickson, Mary. "Antique Gunsmithing" (North America, U.S.), F220, Betsy Adler, 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/44 Hoff, Paul E. "The Amish Buggy: A Study in Craftsmanship" (Ed Hostetler – Buggy Maker, North America, U.S., Indiana, Lagrange County), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, August 19, 1973 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/46 Tranter, Sharon. "Caning" (North America, U.S., Illinois), F220, Jack Day, 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/47 Hansell, Susan. "A Photo Study of the Chalmers Cemetery" (North America, U.S., Indiana, White County), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/48 Crew, R. "The Duckworth Barn" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Owen County), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/49 Warner, Kathleen. "The Sammy Bartlett House." (North America, U.S, Indiana, Lawrence County), F810, Dr. Henry Glassie, July 9, 1971 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/50 Aydt, Douglas J. "Hilltop House" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Morgan County), F384, Dr. Henry Glassie, 1971 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/51 Childs, Barry. "Notes on an Architectural Echo of Dubois County" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), F720, Dr. Warren Roberts, December 12, 1975 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/53 Wheeler, T. R. "Chair Caning" (Hope, Bartholomew County, Indiana), F220, Jens Lund, March 28, 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/54 Ostroff, Frann. "Crocheting in Relation to Folklore" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F220, Rich March, April 22, 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/55 Windnagel, Susan. "Tools and Implements used by early farmers in South Indiana" (Indiana, Owen County, Whitehall), F391, Dr. Warren Roberts, Summer 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/56 Lyle, Jane. "The Seanie Buskirk House" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe county, Elletsville - I-house), F391, Dr. Warren Roberts, 1974 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/57 Christman, Gerald W. "The Last Covered Bridge in Bartholomew County" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Bartholomew County), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/58 Ross, Betsy. "Clothing 1855-1880 in Indiana, Ohio, and Illinois" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Illinois, and Ohio), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, August 2, 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C Yoder, Dennis E. "The Roy H. Schmalz Memorial Museum" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F101, John Vlach (T.A.), Date Unknown (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/60 Freer, Lisa. "How to Run a Sale" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Henry County, Spiceland), F220, Instructor Unknown, Spring 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/61 Unknown Author. No Title (North America, U.S., Kentucky - Broom making in Kentucky), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, October, 13, 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/62 Paynter, Barbara Jo. "An Interview with Mrs. Anna Elliott" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Washington County, Canton - Doll Collection and Repair) Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, October 25, 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/63 Nopar, Andreas. "Cooking Gefilte Fish" (North America, U.S., Illinois, Skokie), F220, Mr. Kash, November 29, 1972 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/64 Tuley, Pamela. "Spanish and Filipino Cookery" (North America, U.S., Illinois, Chicago?), Folk Cookery, Instructor Unknown, April 24, 1973 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/65 Behler, Mary E. "The Bartholomew County Courthouse" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Bartholomew County), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, November 9, 1977 (Box 6)
  - M/C 77/66 Hansen, Cynthia. "Tombstones and Epitaphs" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Porter and Laporte Counties), F101, El-Shamy (?), Nick B. (T.A.?), 1977 (Box 6)
    5 tombstone rubbings stored separately in OS11
  - M/C 77/67 Gunn, Mary Ellen. "A Late 1800's Frame Barn in Santa Claus, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Porter County, Santa Claus), F220, Instructor Unknown, Fall 1975 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/68 Moore, Anne E. "Covered Bridges: Remembrances of a Time Gone By" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Various Counties), F220, Instructor Unknown, April 27, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/69 Miller, Janet. "Quilting," F101, Carl Lindahl, November 22, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/70 Baumbaugh, Cregg B. "Collection Project," F101, Dr. Hasan El-Shamy, June 17, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/71 Coffey, Raymond E. "Folklore Research and Fieldwork Paper," F391, Yence Lund, October 20, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/72 Miller, Teresa L. "The Restoration and Building of Log Cabins and Houses," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, October 20, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/73 Blignaut, James. "Transverse-Crib Barn," F101, Instructor Unknown, November 11, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/74 Wise, Robert. "Subject Proposal," F101, Instructor Unknown, November 17, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/75 Abel, Mark. "Wine Making: Today and Yesterday," CLass # Unknown, Ginny Lee, November 22, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/76 Conrad, Brad. "Grandfather Clock," Class # Unknown, Ginny Lee, November 22, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/77 Friedman, Shelly. "Folklore=Recipes," Class # Unknown, Steve Poyser, November 22, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/78 Medwetz, Steve. "A Tavern: Brewed in Heritage," F101, Instructor Unknown, November 22, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/79 Reisman, Tony. "Folk and Farming," Class # Unknown, Steve Poyser, November 22, 1975 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/80 Zimmerman, James A. "Hunting in Hubbles Corner, Southern Indiana," Class # Unknown, Dr. El-Shamy, Noevmber 22, 1975 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/81 Dolbens, Diane Louise. "The One Room School House [Southern Indiana]," Course Unknown, Warren Roberts, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/82 Polemitou, Olga A.. "Aspects of the Craft of Quilting as Practiced in Southern Indiana," F628, Warren Roberts, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 77/81 Cox, Deborah. "Brown County's Covered Bridges," Course Unknown, Warren Roberts, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/1 Sue, Carter. "Shotgun Collection of Indiana Material Culture" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Fountain, Parke, Wayne Counties), F384, Dr. Warren Roberts, January 5, 1968 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/2 Salo, M. T. "Material Culture of the Ontario Finns" (North America, Canada, Ontario), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/3 Stillabower, Faye E. "Folklore Collection: Indiana Miscellany" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Hendricks County), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/4 Hansen, Calvin. "Examples of Long Island Architecture" (North America, U.S., New York), F384, Dr. Warren Roberts, January 5, 1968 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/5 Black, Judith Ellen. "Illinois Quilters" (North America, U.S., Illinois), F384, Instructor Unknown, 1967 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/6 Brady, Holly. "Transmission of Recipes and Cooking Techniques: A Three Generation Study" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F101, Instructor Unknown, Carl Lindahl (A.I.), November 18, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/7 Myers, Chris. "Contemporary Quilts and Examples" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Hamilton County, Westfield), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, November 22, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/8 Davis, Michael W. "Rabbit Hunting on Sand Mountain" (North America, U.S., Alabama), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, December 9, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/9 Couch, Barbara (Barb). "Indiana Farm Life Eight Years Ago" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F101, El Shamy, Erika Brady (T.A.?), 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/10 French, Gloria. "Baking with Tillie Huffmaster" (North America, U.S., Illinois), F391, Jens Lund, December 1, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/11 Voorheis, Peter. "The Louden House Bloomington, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), F720, Dr. Warren Roberts, Fall 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/12 Duckworth, Ginny. "Food Preservation" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Morgan County, Martinsville), F101, El-Shamy, November 22, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/13 Campbell, Sarah Elizabeth. "The Barn: A Bank Barn Study" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Johnson County, Franklin), F391, Jens Lund, December 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/14 Stacy, Douglas M. "Arts & Crafts" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Johnson County, Edinburg - A Johnson County Craftsman), F390, Jens Lund, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/15 Trittipo, Salinda J. "Significance of Quilt Functions Past and Present" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Marion County, Indianapolis), F101, El-Shamy, November 20, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/16 Kelly, Amy. "An Investigation Into Dutch Cooking" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Dekalb Couty, Auburn), F101, El-Shamy, November 6, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/17 Fhiemann, Carole E. "Bridgeton-Rosedale Covered Bridges in Parke county"(North America, U.S., Indiana, Parke County), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/18 Headley, Steve. "Crafts of the Farrier" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Ellettsville), F101, Instructor Unknown, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/19 Kirshenblatt-Gimblett, Barbara. "Folklife Collected From One Indiana Family" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), Class # Unknown, Dr. Warren Roberts, Fall 1967 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/20 Koss, Andrea. "Applehead Dolls" (North America, U.S., LaPorte County, Valaparaiso, Indiana), F220, Carol Edwards, July 27, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/21 Otto, Chris. "Water Witching in Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Bloomington), F220, Gary Stanton (T.A.), Date Unknown (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/22 Simon and Wendy Bronner. "The Harris House in Ellettsville, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Ellettsville), F720, Dr. Roberts, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/23 Carson, Diane. "Quilts," F220, Instructor Unknown, November 17, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/24 Stilz, Suzie. "Quilting," F101, Instructor Unknown, Carl Lindahl, A.I., April 20, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/25 Premo, Ilknur A. "The Patchwork Quilt," F220, C.L. Edwards, March 24, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/26 Bedan, Kevin. "The Country Store," F101, Roger Beatty, April 18, 1975 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/27 Witty, Charles Otto. "Spencer County Barn," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Summer 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/28 Baker, Greg. "The James F.D. Lanier Home, F220, Instructor Unknown, November 17, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/29 Yeager, John. No Title, F220, Instructor Unknown, April 14, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/30 Pryor, Reed. "Mr. Moore's Cabin, F220, Gary Stanton, November, 20 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/31 Suverkrup, Mark. "Term Project," F220, Instructor Unknown, November 21, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/32 Hayden, Marie. "Connor Prairie Museum, F101, Roger Beatty, Fall 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/33 Scholl, Janet L. "The Art of Broom-making," F101, Dr. El-Shamy, November 14, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/34 Eades,Dan. "One Man and his Crafts," F220, Ellen Polezoes, April 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/35 Coleman, David D. "Tents," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, November 17, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/36 Eades, Amy. "Material Folklore: Essential to Its Maker," F220, Ellen Polezoes, December 12, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/37 Neidigh, Roberta. "Folk Belief Analysis," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Fall 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/38 Garon, Sue. "Maple Syrup Tapping," F101, Steve Poyser, April 21, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/39 Clayton, Laura. "Weaving - Why Does Weaving Still Survive Today?," F101, Dr. El-Shamy/Carl Lindahl, April 28, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/40 Redding, Joan Celeste. "Changes in Quilting," F101, Carl Lindahl, April 24, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 78/41 Karsnick, Kris. "Quilting in America," Class # Unknown, Gary Stanton, April 14, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/1 Raab, Jerry. "Old-Fashioned Hog Butchering" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Reelsville), F101, Instructor Unknown, April 21, 1978 (Box 7)
    (Analog audio cassette CT-A061 removed and stored separately in box 9)
  - M/C 79/2 Hottinger, Chris L. "German-American Recipes" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Muncie), F101, Rikoon, November 20, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/3 Tebbetts, Diane. "The William Blackley House" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), F720, Dr. Warren Roberts, November 29, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/4 Stipp, Mary Margaret. "Farming in the Early 1900s" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Clark County), F391, C. Edwards, November 20, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/5 Miller, Rosemary. "Quilting, Past and Present" (North America, U.S.), F220, Lewis, Gary Stanton (T.A.?), April 14, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/6 Rebecca, Ruder A. "Limestone Carving: A Southern Indiana Tradition" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F220, Professor Lewis, April 14, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C Rockey, Robert D. "A Self-Trained Clock Repairman" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Switzerland County, Vevay), F220, Betsy Adler (A.I.), April 14, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/8 Cody, Rick Gerald. "Basket Making" (North America, U.S., North Carolina, Sylva), F220, Instructor Unknown, April 24, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/9 McLochlin, Marsha. "Soap-making" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Starke County, North Judson), F101, El-Shamy, April 13, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/10 Pratt, Donna F. "Cabinet Making" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/11 Masaw, Angie. "Horse-shoeing: A Historical Analysis" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe, County, Bloomington), F101, El-Shamy, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/12 Doug Hasler. "Process and Social Experience of Threshing" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Greene County), F101, El-Shamy, 1977 (Box 7)
    ( Three nalog audio cassettes removed and stored separately in box 9)
  - M/C 79/13 Becker, Stephen and J.D. McAloon. "A Study of House and Settlement" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F720, Dr. Warren Roberts, Fall 1973 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/14 Roberts, Elizabeth. "The Smith-Wilson House" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F220, Mr. Adler, November 23, 1975 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/15 Henken, Elissa. "The Stallknecht House" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F720, Dr. Warren Roberts, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/16 Stotts, Mary H. "How to Cane a Straight-Sided Chair" (North America, U.S, Indiana), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 26, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/17 Giray, Eren. "An Anatolian Custom in a University Town: Pismaniye Making in Bloomington" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F721, Dr. Warren Roberts, April 30, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/18 Bradley, Martha. "Quilting in Trafalgar, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Johnson County, Trafalgar), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, December 8, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/19 Elsner, Lisa. "Crocheting" (North America, U.S.), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, March 17, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/20 Archer, Sara. "Quilting" (North America, U.S, Indiana, Switzerland County), F220, Instructor Unknown, April 26, 1978 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/21 Schroer, Cande. "Quilts: Classification and Techniques" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Jackson County, Seymour), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, November 22, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/22 Hornbach, Theresa. "Quilting Patterns" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Dearborn County), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Fall, 1977 (Box 7)
  - M/C 79/23 Reed, Rhonda. "Quilting" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Wayne County), F220, Lewis, 1978 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/25 Sichting, Cheryl. "Comparison of Quilters" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Morgan County, Martinsville), F220, Instructor Unknown, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/26 Sanders, Jamie. "Maple Sugaring" (North America, U.S., Owen County, Spence), F220, Instructor Unknown, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/27 Jackson, Joyce M. "Quilting Tradition" (North America, U.S., Louisiana, Zachary), F516, Dorson, Date Unknown (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/28 DeLau, Alan. "Two Broom Makers" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Brown County), F101, El-Shamy, 1977 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/29 Mann, Lisa. "Missouri Foodways and Change" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Lake County, Lowell), F220, Instructor Unknown, April 14, 1978 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/30 Kleopfer, Eric G. "Monroe County Tombstones" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), F101, Dr. Hasan El-Shamy, Roger Beatty (A.I.), Fall 1978 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/31 Larkin, Kimball. "Bloomington Epitaphs" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), F220, Brown, 1978 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/32 Foster, Bruce D. "The Art of Making Maple Syrup" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Bloomington), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 20, 1978 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/33 Whitmore, Ann. "Auctioneering" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Allen County, Decatur), F220, Phyllis Harrison, April 10, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/34 Holtberg, Karen. "Round Barns" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Fulton County) F220, Dr. Lewis, April 6, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/35 Trainor, Amanda. "Functionalism in Quilting," F101, Instructor Unknown, April 19, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/36 Snoddy, William D. "The Barn and an Era Past," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 20, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/37 Leonard, Shawn. "Water Witching," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 20, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/38 Shaffer, Jerry J. "Folklore Custom that is Still Practice[d] Today of Religious Carvings," F220, Professpr Jens Lund, December 5, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/39 Sepulveda, Steve. "A Study on Certain Aspects of Maple Fair," Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 7, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/40 Lipp, Amy. "Folklore Project: Jewish Foods," F101, Erika Brady, Spring 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/41 Moore, Craig. "Folk Cookery," F101, Instructor Unknown, April 17, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 79/42 Smidt, Sally. "Embroidery," F101, S. Poyser, April 4, 1979 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/1 Elsner, Eileen. "German Cookery" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F101, El-Shamy, Ginny Lee (T.A.), November 20, 1977 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/2 Wegener, Tim. "Cemetary Tombstones: A Rural-Town Comparison" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County), F101, Instructor Unknown, November 22, 1977 (Box 8)
  - M/C 80/3 Just, Cindy. "The Spectrum of Quilting" (North America, Indiana, Marion County, Indianapolis), F01, El-Shamy, 1978 (Box 8)